<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Get Your Ticket</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="text_get_your_ticket">Get Your Ticket!</string>
    <string name="text_choose_movie">Choose a movie from the list below...</string>
    <string name="text_view_pirates_description_text">Blacksmith Will Turner teams up with eccentric pirate "Captain" Jack Sparrow to save his love, the governor\'s daughter, from Jack\'s former pirate allies, who are now undead.</string>
    <string name="text_view_movie_name_text">Movie:</string>
    <string name="text_view_movie_text">Movie:</string>
    <string name="text_view_date_text">Date:</string>
    <string name="button_date_picker">...</string>
    <string name="date_picker_example">MM/DD/YYYY</string>
    <string name="text_view_time_text">Time:</string>
    <string name="text_view_name_text">Name:</string>
    <string name="edit_text_phone_text">Phone:</string>
    <string name="text_view_email_text">E-mail:</string>
    <string name="text_view_count_text">Quantity:</string>
    <string name="button_book_text">Book the tickets!</string>
    <string name="pref_default_values">Default values</string>
    <string name="pref_username_title">Default name</string>
    <string name="pref_username_summary">Enter the default name</string>
    <string name="pref_email_title">Default email</string>
    <string name="pref_email_summary">Enter a default email</string>
    <string name="pref_phone_title">Default phone number</string>
    <string name="pref_phone_summary">Enter a default phone number</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_select_date">Select Date</string>
    <string name="button_select_done">Done</string>
    <string name="text_view_success">Your tickets have been successfuly booked!</string>
    <string name="confirmation_summary">%1$s: You have booked %2$s tickets for %3$s at %4$s to see %5$s.</string>
    <string name="text_view_transformers_description_text">Sam Witwicky leaves the Autobots behind for a normal life. But when his mind is filled with cryptic symbols, the Decepticons target him and he is dragged back into the Transformers\' war.</string>
    <string name="text_view_thor_description_text">The powerful but arrogant god Thor is cast out of Asgard to live amongst humans in Midgard (Earth), where he soon becomes one of their finest defenders.</string>
    <string name="text_view_prince_description_text">A young fugitive prince and princess must stop a villain who unknowingly threatens to destroy the world with a special dagger that enables the magic sand inside to reverse time.</string>
    <string name="text_view_iron_description_text">With the world now aware of his identity as Iron Man, Tony Stark must contend with both his declining health and a vengeful mad man with ties to his father\'s legacy.</string>
    <string name="text_view_inception_description_text">A thief who steals corporate secrets through use of dream-sharing technology is given the inverse task of planting an idea into the mind of a CEO.</string>
    <string name="text_view_hobbit_description_text">A reluctant hobbit, Bilbo Baggins, sets out to the Lonely Mountain with a spirited group of dwarves to reclaim their mountain home - and the gold within it - from the dragon Smaug.</string>
    <string name="text_view_eragon_description_text">In his homeland of Alagaesia, a farm boy happens upon a dragon\'s egg -- a discovery that leads him on a predestined journey where he realized he\'s the one person who can defend his home against an evil king.</string>
    <string name="text_view_avengers_description_text">Earth\'s mightiest heroes must come together and learn to fight as a team if they are to stop the mischievous Loki and his alien army from enslaving humanity.</string>
    <string name="text_view_avatar_description_text">A Paraplegic Marine dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission becomes torn between following his orders and protecting the world he feels is his home.</string>

</resources>
